JUNYEONG KIM

Raleigh, NC

Junyeongkim1@gmail.com | (919) 395 - 0270 | Linkedin.com/in/junyeongkim

SUMMARY

A versatile and result-driven student currently finalizing Bachelor of Science degree in Computer Science with a focus in Software Engineering. Well prepared to contribute abilities while further developing acquired skills and gaining real-world experiences. Highly organized, responsible and well-versed in Java, C/C++, Python, JavaScript, HTML5, and CSS with several personal projects. Strong sense of "do it right the first time", meticulous attention to details, and strive to explore new solutions in an efficient way.

EDUCATION

University of North Carolina - Chapel Hill, NC

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

- Dean's List: Fall 2021, Spring 2022
- Golden Door Scholar

Relevant Coursework:

- Data Structures & Algorithms
- · Operating Systems
- · Algorithms & Analysis

Wake Technical Community College - Raleigh, NC

Associate of Science/Engineering

- President's List: Fall 2017, Spring 2019
- Dean's List Fall 2018

Aug 2017 - May 2020

Aug 2020 - May 2023

GPA: 3.9

GPA: 3.9

PROJECTS

Java

• Nonograms: Utilized model-view-controller design pattern together with the JavaFX UI library to design a complete, functioning Graphic User Interface (GUI) implementation of the single-player logic puzzle nonograms. Maven, a build automation tool for Java, was used as a build manager where JavaFX was added as a Maven dependency to the POM file. The project also involved high usage of Object-Oriented Programming where the idea of encapsulation, composition over inheritance, and subtype polymorphism was implemented.

C Language

• Shell Command: Constructed a simple shell in C using the command line interface. The shell itself can change directories and execute system programs such as **pwd** and **Is**.

<u>C++</u>

• Swimming Pool Analysis: Assembled to take user input of the information about swimming pools (length, width, depth) and using them to calculate how much time it takes to fill up the pool with the water flow rate given in Gallons Per Minute.

EXPERIENCE

Arbol - Buffalo, NY

Jul 2022 - Present

Software Engineer Intern

- Design and remodel the current website of growarbol.com to address better user experience and create a responsive website.
- Engage in weekly group meetings to enhance more features on the website and brainstorm additional details to be added.

Red Ventures - Fort Mill, SC

Jun 2021 – Aug 2022

Tech Fellowship

- Engineered a full functioning website for a client using HTML5, CSS, and JavaScript along with the utilization of Google Maps RESTful API.
- Developed personal projects and group projects such as building RPG game and Tic-Tac-Toe game with Python along with a Portfolio page using HTML5, CSS, and JavaScript.

Personal Career Guidance - Raleigh, NC

Jun 2019 - Jun 2022

Tutor

- Advise students to decide on what college major best suits them and engaged in conversations about my personal experiences.
- Designed a unique curriculum focusing on the fundamentals of coding to provide an insight for students wanting to pursue Computer Science as their major and dissected coding problems to gain an in-depth understanding of how a certain program is constructed.

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Skills: Java | Python | C/C++ | JavaScript | HTML5 & CSS | Go | Node.js

Languages (Native Efficiency): Korean, English

Interests: Basketball, Tennis, Machine Learning, Teaching